

# JENNIFER BUNNER

## TECHNICAL KNOWLEDGE

Html & Css/Sass/Scss lavascript React.js, Vue.js, Quasar Node.js, Express.js, npm jQuery, MVC Graphic design & UX-design PHP, Wordpress Ubuntu, Docker MySql, noSQL, sql, Dbeaver Firebase, Firestore AJAX, JSON, REST Api, Github, Git Visual Studio Code Figma, Framer, Zeplin, Agile methods, Scrum

## LANGUAGE SKILLS

Swedish -mother tongue English - fluent French - light conversation Spanish - light conversation

## CONTACT

Email: bunner.jennifer@gmail.com

Telephone: 0735 122431

linkedin.com/in/jenniferbunner810 github.com/iths-jennifer-bunner

## **ABOUT ME**

I love to be creative and have a big passion for design. With knowledge such as teamwork, problem solving and communication as well as an eye for detail, I am used to working at a fast pace and stressful situations. I am flexible and like to and try new ideas. I am not afraid to challenge myself or to share my experiences and spread joy!

Portfolio page: https://www.jenniferbunner.com

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

KVIX AB 2022-NOW

Worked with building and improving internal toolings, such as admin tools, and improved the public web kvix.se

## **INTERNSHIP 2**

**ZIGNSEC V6-20 2021** 

I was commissioned to make a new portal with improved UI, than the existing one written in Angular, with the aim that the new portal will start to be used on their new platform, I have together with another student designed mockups to code the portal in React.js, Sass, and material.ui. We worked towards an API on their existing database to retrieve information

### INTERNSHIP 1

#### EVIDENT (HTTPS://EVIDENT.CAPITAL/) V34-41 2020

A startup in the fintech industry. Where I had the main responsibility for making their marketing page (from design to deployment). Available at: https://bocapital.se/ I have designed the page in figma and then coded it in vue.js using Quasar framework and Sass / scss. Have translated it using i18n and installed mailchimp.

## **EDUCATION**

**IT HÖGSKOLAN 2019-2021** 

Frontend developer. See Technical Knowledge to see what I have studied.



## JENNIFER BUNNER

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **GINA TRICOT**

#### Visual merchandiser 100406-ongoing

Responsible for Gina Tricot's concept being visualized and optimized in the store. Store windows (styling, decoration), styling mannequins, campaign follow-up, placement of goods and work with different surfaces in the store, work with purchase proposals, follow-up of sales and make sure the right product is in the right place, inform staff about our campaigns and trends. Helped to open new stores and at new openings.

#### MANGO

#### Visual merchandiser 070801-100401

As part of the management team, I was responsible for the visuals inside the store. Prepare and take out new purchase proposals in the store and style mannequins. Responsible for achieving sales goals and making analyzes of sales. Inform the staff about trends and our campaigns. Hold meetings on upcoming trends and materials science.

#### MQ

#### Visual merchandiser 040201-070713

Responsible for shop windows and all mannequins. Responsible for the visuals in the store, prepare and take out new purchase proposals in the store. Helped to open new stores and at new openings in other stores. Inform the staff about our campaigns and trends.

#### MΩ

#### Salesperson 030122-040201

Responsible for complaints and returns. Purchaser of accessories (scarves and belts from the brand Atlas), and for Fornarina. Managed the store's clearings (send returns and complaints back to the dealer).

## OTHER EDUCATION

**FOLKUNIVERSITET**; 2008

Drawing and crouqis

#### FOLKUNIVERSITETET; 2008

Illustration

## COURS DE CIVILISATION FRANCAIS DE LA SORBONNE; 2009-2010

FRANS SCHARTAU; 2009-2010

Business administration

#### **ENSKILDA GYMNASIET; 1995-2000**

Secondary school and Socio-economic program - upper secondary diploma

## **REFERENCES**

Given at request